Ibrahim Ismail Alisi



Contact

(00962) 078 079 6000 Ibrahim.i.alisi@gmail.com

AMMAN, JORDAN

Skills

- Strategic planning
- **Process & Systems Design**
- Risk Management
- **Process implementation**
- Change Management
- Training & Development
- Proficient in Microsoft excel
- HR Best Practices

Education

Master's degree, MBA (2017) University of Petra, Amman Jordan

Bachelor's degree, Accounting (2009) University of Petra, Amman Jordan

Professional Certificates

Certified Human Resources Manager, **CHRM (2022)** From The Global Association for Quality Management (GAQM)®, UK

Summary

Experienced Professional with over (14) years of experience in management. Who translates business vision into SOPs that improve performance, profitability, growth, and employee engagement, translates visions and strategies into actionable, value-added goals. Possess strong analytical, leadership and communication skills, Able to meet and exceed goals in any environment.

Experience

Administrative Quality Control Manager 1987



International Pioneers Academy Schools (01/2022 - 01/2024)

- Setting and implementing internal/external quality requirements to ensure company services meet customer expectations.
- Establish procedures and processes for sampling, recording and reporting of quality data.

Administrative & HR Manager

International Pioneers Academy Schools (12/2019 - 01/2022)

- Hiring, training, and evaluating employees and taking corrective action when necessary.
- Developing, reviewing, and improving administrative systems, policies, and procedures.
- Working with the accounting and management teams to set budgets, monitor spending, and process payroll and other expenses.
- Supervising the day-to-day operations the administrative department and staff members.

Assistant Manager

International Pioneers Academy Schools (11/2014 - 12/2019)

Accountant & HR Officer

- ** International Pioneers Academy Schools (03/2012 11/2014)
- ** Almas Water Factory (10/2010 8/2011)



** Rum Industrial Gases Company (12/2009 - 10/2010)



Training courses

Legal HR Diploma, Excellence Standards

TOT, COSO, ISO9001, Internal Audit